

export const whyGridArr = [ 

{
    title: " we are here to support you",
    content: "Your business's prosperity relies on the effectiveness of your website. It acts as a crucial instrument for brand building, customer attraction, and revenue generation. Through our care plans, you can have complete confidence that your website will operate flawlessly around the clock, without any interruptions."

},
{
    title: "keep things running smooth",
    content: "Carrying out scheduled maintenance and backups for a website demands both time and specialized skills. The consequences of errors in these activities can be financially burdensome. We handle all the essential upkeep, freeing you to concentrate on what you excel at: overseeing your business operations."
},
{
    title: "assistance whenever you need it",
    content: "In the event of any issues with your website, it is crucial to have timely solutions and swift resolutions. That's precisely where our expertise shines. Trust your website to our capable team and be confident that we are here to support you, even when you're not actively seeking assistance."
},

]

export const whatGridArr = [ 

{
    title: "software updates",
    content: "In the event of any issues with your website, it is crucial to have timely solutions and swift resolutions. That's precisely where our expertise shines. Trust your website to our capable team and be confident that we are here to support you, even when you're not actively seeking assistance."

},
{
    title: "website backups",
    content: "Though it may not be pleasant to consider, websites are vulnerable to malware infections and ransomware attacks. To mitigate these risks, we conduct daily backups of your website, both offline and online. In the unfortunate event of an attack, we can promptly restore your website to its previous version, minimizing any potential downtime."
},
{
    title: "security and privacy",
    content: "More than 50,000 websites get hacked each day although less than 10% of these sites are custom websites. Most of those hacked are due to the sites not being maintained properly. We’ve invested in the proper firewalls and other security precautions to make sure your website is secure and protected against threats."
},
{
    title: "web analytics",
    content: "When a task holds significance, it deserves assessment. Web analytics offer a means to measure your website's performance, offering valuable insights into customer behavior. By optimizing the user experience and improving conversions, we will handle the setup of web analytics for you. This will empower you to effortlessly obtain actionable insights and make informed decisions."
},
{
    title: "professional web support",
    content: "Our Web Development  experts are available to answer your questions and help you accomplish your goals. You tell us what you need in terms of functionality, and we’ll figure out how to get it done. We love a challenge."
},
{
    title: "top tier hosting",
    content: "Given that your business relies on your website, any interruption in service can lead to missed opportunities. Our commitment to round-the-clock monitoring guarantees an impressive uptime rate of 99%. Moreover, our servers are equipped with redundant backup locations, providing added reliability. You can place your trust in our hosting services, knowing that we prioritize dependability and ensure a seamless online presence for your business."
}

]

export const CarePlansFaqs = [
    {
      question:"why do I need a care plan?",
      answer:"If your website is built on the WordPress platform, then the answer is yes.It is crucial to understand that WordPress itself is not at fault. The platform's rapid growth has led to the existence of over 55,000 WordPress add-ons, also known as plugins. Given that WordPress powers over 43% of the internet, it has inevitably become a prime target for hackers worldwide.In addition, regular maintenance is indispensable for all websites. Similar to cars, routine tasks such as oil changes, tire rotations, and necessary repairs are essential for a dependable journey from point A to B. Our care plans encompass these critical components.Based on our expertise, a comprehensive WordPress Care Plan should include:Weekly plugin updates, 24/7 uptime monitoring, Security scans, Performance scans and Daily backups."
    },
    {
      question:"I have a simple website do I need software updates?",
      answer:"Regularly updating website software is of utmost importance for both functionality and security reasons. Functionality: Software updates often include bug fixes, performance enhancements, and new features that improve the overall functionality of your website. By keeping your website software up to date, you ensure that it operates smoothly, providing a seamless experience for your users. Updates can also enhance compatibility with the latest web technologies, ensuring that your website remains compatible with modern browsers and devices. Security: One of the most critical reasons to update website software is to protect against security vulnerabilities. Hackers constantly search for weaknesses in website software, and outdated versions are often targeted. Software updates often address security vulnerabilities and provide patches to fix them, safeguarding your website from potential breaches and data compromises. Regular updates ensure that you have the latest security measures in place, reducing the risk of unauthorized access and maintaining the trust of your users. By staying proactive with software updates, you not only maintain the optimal functionality of your website but also bolster its security, mitigating potential risks and keeping your online presence robust and reliable."
    },
    {
      question:"where are some common issues covered by the maintenance and care plans?",
      answer:"some of the top care plan requests since 2017 include :Rollback website to the previous version, Plugin conflict, Website brought back up after an outage, Security issue, SSL expired, DNS changes, Use of our software licenses, Website email deliverability fixed, Software license expiration detected."
    },
    {
      question:"can I cancel at any time?",
      answer:"When we bring your website onto our care plan, significant attention is dedicated to ensuring a proper setup, updating and stabilizing all software, and uncovering any potential issues. To account for the time and effort invested in getting your website up to speed, we require a three-month commitment for our care plan. Following the initial commitment period, you have the flexibility to cancel at any time before the end of your billing cycle."
    },
    {
      question:"what if there additional features that need to be added in the middle of a project?",
      answer:" A comprehensive discovery process helps reduce the need for scope changes, although project priorities may shift during its execution. If any new functionality, design elements, or content are introduced that were not initially outlined in the agreement, it will usually necessitate adjustments to the budget and timeline. However, rest assured that we will reach a mutual agreement on any changes to the budget and timeline before initiating any additional work."
    },
    {
      question:"do you give discounts for multiple websites?",
      answer:"We give a 10% discount for 501(c) organizations."
    },
    {
      question:"are there any hidden charges?",
      answer: "Everything listed above is included in our care and maintenance plans. We don’t charge any hidden fees. If anything is unclear now or in the future please contact us at contact@webambrosia.com"
    },
    {
        question:"what happens if there’s a fire, a flood or a malware attack at your server’s location?",
        answer: " we use chemiclouds cloud based hosting your website will be backed up on multiple different servers across the US. There is also a daily physical backup in a seperate location. You are in good hands and there is nothing to worry about."
    },
    {
        question:"Is your hosting US based?",
        answer: "We collaborate with ChemiCloud, one of the leading C-panel hosting providers globally. Our selection process includes identifying a data center in close proximity to your target audience, ensuring optimal speed. Additionally, we can implement a content delivery network to further enhance performance. Why do we choose to partner with ChemiCloud? Simply put, other inexpensive solutions like GoDaddy, Hostgator, Bluehost, and similar providers cannot match ChemiCloud's exceptional standards in terms of performance, security, and support. They operate in an entirely different league altogether."
    },
    {
        question:"do you provide email hosting?",
        answer: "Opting for a web design agency to host your email may feel outdated, reminiscent of the past. Instead, we suggest considering cloud-based solutions like Microsoft Office 365 or Google Workspace for your email hosting needs.At our agency, we utilize Microsoft 365 and are more than willing to provide guidance if you decide to go with them. By choosing to directly pay the service provider, you can access their competitive rates and leverage their support systems. Remember, maintaining email consistency entails using an email address associated with your website's URL. This means avoiding free accounts from platforms like Hotmail or Gmail."
    },
    {
        question:"where are your care plan representatives located?",
        answer: "Our team is headquartered in Albany, NY, with our team working from their home-based offices in the USA, support requests go to a US based team member to make sure action is taken quickly and effectively.You can email us at contact@webambrosia.com or call (518) 932-1392 for support."
    },
    {
        question:"how long will it take to setup my website hosting and maintenance plan?",
        answer: "We will set you up in three to four business days."
    },
    {
        question:"I received a domain name renewal in the mail. is it a scam ?",
        answer: "Almost certainly. Domain name renewal notices usually only come in email and should be sent from your existing domain registrar."
    },
    {
        question:"will you renew our domain for us?",
        answer: "We believe our clients should always take direct ownership and make payment of their domain name.A domain name is the most important point of access to your website and more valuable than the website itself (if the website is backed up somewhere that is). After all, if someone else takes control of your domain, they can point it anywhere. And your emails wouldn't work anymore. Since a domain name typically costs $15 or less per year we recommend renewing your domain name for five (5) years at a time and putting several notices in your calendar about the future renewal. It really is so important.."
    },
    {
        question:" I received a suspicious email about issues with my website, what should I do?",
        answer: "In most cases, these emails are generated by automated robots, sending out generic lists of issues that may not even pertain to your specific website. They often present solutions in an attempt to gain you as a client. If you have any doubts, it is advisable to reach out to your trusted web designer or developer to verify the legitimacy of the email. Remember, no website is flawless, and having someone you know and trust investigate the matter is the best course of action."
    },
  
  ]
  
  
  
  